

#### DATE/PLACE OF BIRTH

#### 06-07-99

Reliance Hospital & Maternity Oba, Anambra state Nigeria.

#### **INTERNSHIPS**

#### **Sunny V Computer**

2021 Port Harcourt

Sales-Maintainance-Repairs

- Troubleshoot and diagnose clients computer professionally for effective repairs and maintenance.
- Maintaining good seller/buyer relationships
- Replacement of computer parts & accessories

### **SKILLS**

PERSONAL · Good communication ·

Ability to work in a team · Fast learner ·

Adaptability · High teaching efficiency

TECH · Javascript · SCSS · HTML · CSS ·

ReactJS

COMPUTER · Microsoft office ·

Hardware & software · Troubleshooting ·

Operating system · Digital marketing ·

Networking

### **MY TIME**

Designing

Coding

Vidoe Game

Internet

# IGWE ANTHONY C.

## IT & COMPUTER TECHNICIAN

+234 (805) -979-8898 @ tonychinaza40@gmail.com

Port Harcourt, Nigeria.

#### **PROFILE**

Dedicated worker and instructor with excellent communication, time management and computer skills with experiences of almost half a decade. Aiming to leverage my abilities to successfully fill the vacancy at your company. Frequently praised as hardworking by my peers, I can be relied upon to help your company achieve its goals.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### NATIONAL DIPLOMA

2018 - 2020

Owerri

Federal Polytechnic Nekede

Computer Science

SSCE/WAEC 2010 - 2016

## Niger Grammar School

· Honors - Senior Prefect

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## IT Technician

2017 - 2018

Port Harcourt

#### V.S.A Concept Ltd

Port Harcourt

An A-list Tech company deals on sales, repairs & maintainance of computers and gadgets

- Inspected and diagnosed issues with equipments to find solutions.
- Assisted with installing, maintaining and troubleshooting faulty computers and applications.
- Created training materials and procedures to maintain optimal functionality. Inspected and diagnosed issues with equipments to find solutions.

### Computer Technician

2016 - 2017

#### Folks Supermarket

Port Harcourt

A self-service shop offering a wide variety of food, beverages and household products, organized into sections

- Inspected and diagnosed issues with digital sales equipment to determine appropriate solutions.
- Consulted with other technicians on major hardware and software issues to find
- Reassembled computers after making repairs and replacing parts.
- Reinstalled software programs and adjusted settings on existing software fixed machine malfunctions.

#### **COURSES**

### FrontEnd Web Development

### Computer Maintainance

2022 - Rivers State ICT center, Port Harcourt

2014/16 - V.S.A Concept Ltd, Port Harcourt

🔀 Enhancv

## LANGUAGES

Igbo

Native



English

Proficient



## FIND ME ONLINE

WhatsApp
+234 (703) 060-6001

Instagram
@\_thatboynaz

## REFERENCES



### Mr. Anene Samuel

Detective, Nigerian Police Force 07063078725



## Mrs. Antonia Ijeoma Onyema

CEO IJ Real Fashion 08036659751

